[
 {
   "question": "harrituta",
   "answer": "amazed"
 },
 {
   "question": "haserre",
   "answer": "angry"
 },
 {
   "question": "gaiztoa",
   "answer": "bad"
 },
 {
   "question": "handia",
   "answer": "big"
 },
 {
   "question": "aspergarria",
   "answer": "boring"
 },
 {
   "question": "puskatuta",
   "answer": "broken"
 },
 {
   "question": "garbi",
   "answer": "clean"
 },
 {
   "question": "itxita",
   "answer": "closed"
 },
 {
   "question": "zikin",
   "answer": "dirty"
 },
 {
   "question": "azkarra",
   "answer": "fast"
 },
 {
   "question": "tentela",
   "answer": "fool"
 },
 {
   "question": "ona",
   "answer": "good"
 },
 {
   "question": "pozik",
   "answer": "happy"
 },
 {
   "question": "maiteminduta",
   "answer": "in love"
 },
 {
   "question": "interesgarria",
   "answer": "interesting"
 },
 {
   "question": "luzea",
   "answer": "long"
 },
 {
   "question": "etzanda",
   "answer": "lying down"
 },
 {
   "question": "urduri",
   "answer": "nervous"
 },
 {
   "question": "berria",
   "answer": "new"
 },
 {
   "question": "polita",
   "answer": "pretty"
 },
 {
   "question": "gizena",
   "answer": "obese"
 },
 {
   "question": "zaharra",
   "answer": "old"
 },
 {
   "question": "triste",
   "answer": "sad"
 },
 {
   "question": "beldurtuta",
   "answer": "scared"
 },
 {
   "question": "motza",
   "answer": "short"
 },
 {
   "question": "baxua",
   "answer": "low"
 },
 {
   "question": "eserita",
   "answer": "sitting"
 },
 {
   "question": "mantsoa",
   "answer": "slow"
 },
 {
   "question": "txikia",
   "answer": "small"
 },
 {
   "question": "argia",
   "answer": "smart"
 },
 {
   "question": "zutik",
   "answer": "standing"
 },
 {
   "question": "altua",
   "answer": "tall"
 },
 {
   "question": "argala",
   "answer": "thin"
 },
 {
   "question": "nekatuta",
   "answer": "tired"
 },
 {
   "question": "itsusia",
   "answer": "ugly"
 },
 {
   "question": "bustita",
   "answer": "wet"
 },
 {
   "question": "gazte",
   "answer": "young"
 },
 {
   "question": "arrosa",
   "answer": "pink"
 },
 {
   "question": "beltza",
   "answer": "black"
 },
 {
   "question": "berdea",
   "answer": "green"
 },
 {
   "question": "gorria",
   "answer": "red"
 },
 {
   "question": "horia",
   "answer": "yellow"
 },
 {
   "question": "laranja",
   "answer": "orange"
 },
 {
   "question": "marroia",
   "answer": "brown"
 },
 {
   "question": "morea",
   "answer": "purple"
 },
 {
   "question": "urdina",
   "answer": "blue"
 },
 {
   "question": "zuria",
   "answer": "white"
 }
]